

610 Purdue Mall, West Lafayette, IN, 47907

□ (415)203-8543 | ☑ chi45@purdue.edu | 🏕 hyung-gun.me | 📮 stnoah1 | 🛅 hyung-gun

Research Interests

My research interests lie at the intersection of Computer Vision and Robotics, focusing on 3D Geometric Deep Learning for recognizing and synthesizing 3D objects. In this area, I applied machine learning (deep learning) algorithms for Augmented/Virtual Reality and Smart Factory.

Education

Purdue University West Lafayette, IN, USA

MASTER OF SCIENCE IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

· Advisor: Karthik Ramani, Donald W.Feddersen Professor of Mechanical Engineering

Yonsei University Seoul, South Korea

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

• Advisor: Soo-Hong Lee, Full Professor of Mechanical Engineering

• 2011-2013, 2-year military service

Skills_

Programming Python, C/C++, Matlab, SQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, PHP

Frameworks TensorFlow, Keras, Caffe, PyTorch, ROS

Software Creo Parametric, SolidWorks, HyperWorks, GAZEBO

Publications and Patents

Conference Proceedings

- [C2][PDF] H. Hwang, H. G. Chi, S. H. Lee. (2017) "A Research about 3D Design Data Classification with 3D Convolutional Neural Network", Proceedings of the Society for Computational Design and Engineering Conference, pp. 441-442.
- [C1][PDF] M. H. Woo, S. H. Kim, H. G. Chi, M. W. Park, J. K. Kim and S. H. Lee. (2016) "Development of Web-based, Module Structure Platform for Surgical Workflow Management", Proceedings of the Society for Computational Design and Engineering Conference, pp. 439-441.

Journal Papers

- [J5][PDF] S. Kim, H. G. Chi and Karthik Ramani. "Object synthesis by learning part geometry with multi-tasks" (2019) Computers & Graphics, submitted.
- [J4][PDF] S. Kim, N. Winovich, H. G. Chi, G. Lin and and Karthik Ramani. "Latent Transformations Neural Network for Object View Synthesis" (2019) The Visual Computer, under revision at editor's request.
- [J3][PDF] L.Paredes, X. Qian, H. G. Chi and Karthik Ramani. "ControllAR: Design and Fabrication of a Universal Parametric Low-Profile Hand Wearable for Augmented Reality Interactions" (2019) Proceedings of the ACM on Interactive, Mobile, Wearable and Ubiquitous Technologies (IMWUT), submitted.
- [J2][PDF] H. T. Hwang, H. G. Chi, N. K. Kang, H. B. Kong and Soo-Hong Lee. "An Evaluation Methodology for 3D Deep Neural Network using Visualization in 3D Data Classification" (2019) Journal of Mechanical Science and Technology (JMST), 33(3), pp. 1333-1339.
- [J1][PDF] JIN YONGZHU, H. G. Chi and Soo-Hong Lee. (2016). A Study on the Optimal Design of Pedestrian Robots Using Jansen Mechanism. Korean Journal of Computational Design and Engineering, 22(2), pp. 18-22.

• [P1][PDF] H. G. Chi. "Computer Input Automation System" KR Patent (2017): 10-1745330.

Research Experience

Mechanical Net

C-design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE ASSISTANT

Jan. 2019 - Present

Aug. 2018 - PRESENT

Mar. 2010 - Feb. 2017

- Collected massive mechanical component CAD data with a web-scrapper, and expanded the data for dense data distribution using Creo Parametric and SolidWorks API.
- Developed a web-based 3D CAD search engine using a 3D Deep Neural Network and PostgreSQL database.

FuseNet C-design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE ASSISTANT

Aug. 2018 - Present

- · Built a Generative Adversarial Network which generates 3D objects given a discrete category condition and continuous instance-level attributes by fusing the various types of geometric information.
- Introduced a part identifier module which learns part geometry to preserve part properties of 3D objects. (Relevant publication: [J5])

AUGUST 16, 2019 HYUNG-GUN CHI · CURRICULUM VITAE

Latent Transformation Neural Network (LTNN)

C-design LAB, Purdue Univ.

Graduate Assistant Aug. 2018 - Feb. 2019

• Developed a fully-convolutional conditional generative network which is capable of view synthesis using a light-weight neural network suited for real-time applications. Introduced the conditional transformation unit which is designed to learn the latent space transformations corresponding to specified target views. (*Relevant publication:* [*J4*])

Visual Programming Language for Mobile Robots and IoT Nodes

C-design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE ASSISTANT

Aug. 2018 - Apr. 2019

- Proposed a web-based visual and spatial programming language that allows novice users and small industries to program mobile robots and IoT Nodes to execute planned tasks.
- Developed a virtual world using Robotic Operating System(ROS) and GAZEBO which simulates interaction between mobile robots and IoT devices.

ControllAR C-design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE ASSISTANT

Aug. 2018 - Dec. 2018

• Proposed a parametrizing interface, simple and accessible fabrication workflow, and a pressure sensor using a soft piezoresistive elastomer material. Also, developed embedded system using Arduino and analyzed signals from different sensors and materials. (Relevant publication: [J3])

3D Objects Classification Model Evaluation

Knowledge-Based Design LAB, Yonsie Univ.

Undergraduate Research Assistant

Feb. 2016 - Jul. 2017

Proposed an evaluation method for 3D Deep Neural Networks by visualizing the impact of each voxel of each 3D objects and also a
web-based 3D CAD search engine using a 3D Deep Neural Network for demonstration. (Relevant publication: [J2][C2])

Web-based Surgical Workflow Management Platform

Knowledge-Based Design LAB, Yonsie Univ.

Undergraduate Research Assistant

Feb. 2016 - Aug. 2016

• Developed a web-based interface and database for integrated surgical information, to optimize surgical procedures and reduce the medical loss caused by communication errors and lack of information. (*Relevant publication:* [C1])

Working Experience

Python Developer

Seoul, South Korea

FINANCIAL INSIGHT

Jan. 2018 - Jul. 2018

• Worked as a Python developer in an early-stage startup company. Developed a web-scrapper and database for collecting financial data of the Korean stock market.

Python Developer and CEO

Seoul, South Korea

NEIL LAB CORPORATION

Sep. 2016 - Dec. 2017

- Developed an office automation system using Python specifically for automating tasks such as sending an e-mail or issuing receipts, and designed a back-end system and database for customer web-service which automatically scrap and integrate customer's financial and personal data. (*Relevant patent:* [P1])
- Founded and led a startup company as a CEO for a year and also worked as a Python developer. The company was funded \$ 30,000 by the Seongnam Industry Promotion Agency.

Mechanic and Squad leader

Inje, South Korea

REPUBLIC OF KOREA ARMY

Apr. 2011 – Jan. 2013

- Maintained military weapons and equipment including firearms and vehicles.
- Led a squad as a squad leader; honored as a distinguished soldier.

Honors & Awards

KISTI (Korea Institute of Science and Technology Information) President's Award,

Seoul, South Korea

Edison Challenge – Computer Aided Design Section

d,

CDE (Korea Society for Computational Design and Engineering) President's Award, CDE Challenge – Computational Design and Engineering Tools Section

Daejeon, South Korea

Extracurricular Activity

Habitat for Humanity Korea Campus Chapter

South Korea

Member & President

2016

Mar. 2010 - Aug. 2016

• Constructed new houses for the homeless and renovated old houses, served more than 500 hours.

• Led and managed a volunteer group for a year; received the first honor from 2014 Yonsei Club Evaluation.

Korea Food for the Hungry International - campus volunteer group

South Korea

2

MEMBER

Apr. 2013 - Nov. 2013

• Mentored preschool children and elementary school students at the Seoul Children's Center

AUGUST 16, 2019 HYUNG-GUN CHI · CURRICULUM VITAE